[
    {
        "question": "Q1: What is the correct full form of SASS?",
        "a":"Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets",
        "b":"Systematic Awesome Style Sheets",
        "c":"Symbolic Asymmetric Style Sheets",
        "d":"None of the above.",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q2: Who is the designer of SASS?",
        "a":"James Gosling",
        "b":"Hampton Catlin",
        "c":"Guido van Rossum",
        "d":"Misko Hevery",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q3: How many ways we can use Sass in our application?",
        "a":"We can use Sass in our application as a command-line tool.",
        "b":"We can use Sass in our application as a standalone Ruby module.",
        "c":"We can use Sass in our application as a plugin for any Rack-enabled framework.",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q4: Which of the following directive is used to share rules and relationships between selectors in SASS?",
        "a":"@extend",
        "b":"@media",
        "c":"@extend",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q5: Which of the following are the most attractive features of SASS?",
        "a":"SASS is more stable, powerful, and fully compatible with CSS3.",
        "b":"SASS is time-saving because it facilitates users to write CSS in less code.",
        "c":"SASS uses its syntax.",
        "d":"All of the above.",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q6: Which of the following directive is used to set the style rule to different media types?",
        "a":"@media",
        "b":"@import",
        "c":"@extend",
        "d":"@debug",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q7: Which of the following is the main reason behind using SASS?",
        "a":"SASS facilitates us to write codes easily and efficiently, and they are easy to maintain",
        "b":"SASS is a pre-processing language that provides its syntax.",
        "c":"SASS is a superset of CSS that contains all CSS features and is an open-source pre-processor coded in Ruby.",
        "d":"All of the above.",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q8:What are the key features of SASS?",
        "a":"SASS is a CSS pre-processor with syntax advancements and an extension of CSS3.",
        "b":"SASS has two syntaxes. The first syntax is SCSS, and it uses the .scss extension.",
        "c":"SASS supports language extensions such as nesting, variables, and mixins.",
        "d":"All of the above.",
        "ans":"ans4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q9: Which of the following directive is used to display the SassScript expression value as a fatal error?",
        "a":"@error",
        "b":"@warn",
        "c":"@at-root",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q10: What is the correct way to define a variable in SASS?",
        "a":"$primary-color: #888",
        "b":"@primary-color: #888",
        "c":"%primary-color: #888",
        "d":"#primary-color: #888",
        "ans":"ans1"
    }
]